Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Film and Video, circa 1937-1987 and undated
  - Film, 1936-1979
    - Year at Duke leftover, 1937-1938
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: (film very scratched); Subtitle-East Duke Bldg; Subtitle-West Duke Bldg; Giles Dorm; East Campus Library; Scenes of the 95th Commencement; Reception held on East Campus honoring graduating seniors; Picture of President Flowers walking; Following number of distinguished people; Procession people in academic gown; Numbered: 22
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0089)
    - Year at Duke leftover, 1937-1938
      1 film reel: col.; 5 inch.; From Description of Films: (soft focus); Band goes through different formations on field; Numbered: 24
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0091)
    - Duke Football, 1937-1941; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:06:43
      1 film reel: b&w; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: Duke (86) taking a kick (11) & (20) around him; () passes down to (45) who catches and made a 5 yard gain; Ball goes out; (38) coming up field; One team wearing helmet with white X mark other team sort of a white dome on it; Both uniforms look identical; X team has ball (30) passing out to his right to (37) who runs out of bounds; Game took place in Duke outdoor stadium; (30) passing long down to (41) incompleted pass; Numbered: 42
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0103)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0056, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0103.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0056, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0103.mp4)
    - Football Highlights, 1938; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:01:15
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0110)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0059, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0110.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0059, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0110.mp4)
    - Duke University Highlights, 1938
      print made 1976
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 38, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0242)
    - Centennial Year, 1938-1939; 16mm, black-and-white and color, silent; 0:29:26
      From an Initial Appraisal of this film, a copy of which is in Folder 13, Box 17: Events during the Fall Semester (about 10 minutes); Homecoming parade in Durham; Alumni Reunion and Barbecue; Residential quads with homecoming signs and displays; Duke-Georgia Tech football game; Boxing match; Duke-NCSU baseball game; Spring on the campus (lead-in to Centennial); The Centennial Weekend, Apr. 21-23, 1939 (about 15 minutes); Friday:; Reception of delegates, H. M. Wriston speaks; Dedication of the Sarah P. Duke Gardens, band concert; Saturday a.m.: Education and the public; Trustees of Duke University and Duke Endowment; President Few introduces J. M. Finley (?); Speech by Edouard Benes; Saturday p.m.: The University and the Nation; Speakers; Dean Wannamaker introduces P. H. Hanes; P. F. Hanes hands packet to President Few to be opened in 100 years; Sunday a.m.:; Chapel Service; Portrait of the celebrants; Audience for Carillon concert by Anton Brees; Year-end ceremonies (about 5 minutes); May Day Pageant, The Woman's College; The 87th Commencement:; Representatives of orphanages preparing to lay wreath on JBD's tomb; Alumni registration and luncheon; Commencement ceremony; Family groups receiving degrees (twins, mother-daughter); Honorary degree recipients; Lowering of the flag; Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-14; Reference Copy: DVD. UA88-57-14
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 18, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0004)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0021, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0004.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0021, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0004.mp4)
    - McAfee, circa 1939
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0112)
    - McAfee, circa 1939
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0113)
    - May Festival, 1940; 16mm, color, silent; 0:05:18
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0142)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0071, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0142.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0071, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0142.mp4)
    - Duke 140 Reel 1, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0005)
    - Duke 140 Reel 1 (of 2), 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0006)
    - Duke 140 Reel 2, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0007)
    - Duke 140 A Roll, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0008)
    - Duke 140 A Roll, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0009)
    - Duke 140 Soundtrack Final transfer Part One, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0010)
    - Duke 140 Soundtrack Final transfer Part Two, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0011)
    - Duke 140 Old Original, 1940s
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0013)
    - Campus Scenes, 1941; 16mm, black-and-white and color, silent; 0:11:46
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; In the Description of Films, Number 35 is entitled Life at Duke, 1941. The contents are listed as: Robert L. Flowers elected President of Duke; Executive Committee members met in front of Chapel; Alumnae-Alumni Weekend; Track, Baseball Duke defeats UNC 6-2 final game; May Day Fiesta-lots of color; Commencement; Academic procession; Introduction of Robert L. Flowers as President of Duke; Alumni Luncheon; Degrees conferred in University gym; Numbered: 35
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0101)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0055, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0101.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0055, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0101.mp4)
    - Year at Duke, 1941-1944
      1 film reel: col.; 7 inch.; The dates 1941-42 and 1944 were both written on the original can in which this film was stored. The date 1944 is written on the reel. The typed Description of Films gives the date of reel 38 as 1941. From Description of Films: Color Homecoming Display; Someone reading to group of students; Sign which reads: Notre Dame tried it, Auburn tried it, Navy tried it, Duke DOOD IT!; Another sign,Welcome Brothers!; Picnic or something; People sitting around eating something; Football field; Band and Navy squadron; American flag; Shot of crowd; Navy marches off field; Duke 58.3-Carolina Pre-flight 67.7; Track meet; Somebody out distancing the rest of crowd; Pole Vaulter; Several Pole Vaulters; Sign says Cornelius Warmerdam world champion pole vault clears the 13'6" mark; Here he comes; People running broad jump; Duke-Navy ROTC holds annual review; Marching on field; COLOR medals are presented for highest navigation and marksmanship; Alumni-Alumnae Luncheon; People eating; Commencement Scenes May 18th and 19th, 1942; Reception honoring graduating class and their parents; People in garden BLACK AND WHITE; Senior class lowers flag at sunset; 1896 Reunion Dinner BLACK AND WHITE; Class of '41; Some members of classes of '32, '33, '34, '35; Group standing in front of chapel; Bishop Aden W. Leonard delivers commencement address at chapel; 800 degrees conferred; Academic procession (very dark); Numbered: 38
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0240)
    - Marine Laboratory, circa 1941; 16mm, black-and-white and color, silent; 0:09:57
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 18, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0122)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0062, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0122.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0062, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0122.mp4)
    - Reel C: Duke WWII footage, Rose Bowl Football, includes footage from 1969 Allen Building Takeover, 1942; 1969-02; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:08:41
      1 film reel: 7 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0072)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0046, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0072.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0046, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0072.mp4)
    - Orange Bowl Halftime, circa 1942; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:14
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Float in the center of the football field. It's turning around; Bands in the middle of field-lots of activity out on field, floats leave field; Very dark. 200 ft. long; Numbered: 5
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0075)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0006, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0075.mov)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0006, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0075.mp4)
    - Dance Scenes, 1946-04; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:18
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0136)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0065, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0136.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0065, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0136.mp4)
    - Old Homecoming Scenes, 1946-10-04; 16mm, black-and-white and color, silent; 0:02:14
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 7, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0235)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0140, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0235.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0140, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0235.mp4)
    - Old homecoming scenes taken from yr. at Duke, 1948; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:40
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0137)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0066, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0137.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0066, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0137.mp4)
    - Duke Bands, 1948-1950
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 17, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0012)
    - Inauguration, 1949-10-21
      1 film reel: color, 7 inch
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 38, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0241)
    - A Year at Duke, 1950; 16mm, color, silent; 0:04:21
      1 film reel: 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Aerial view of Duke West Campus; Football field; One of the quads; East Campus; Aerial view of East Campus; Senior class raises flag to open academic year; Flag being presented to Hollis Edens; Flag being raised up pole; Annual Homecoming-students erect homecoming decorations; Duke vs. Virginia; Decorations finish out reel; Numbered: 26
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0093)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0052, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0093.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0052, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0093.mp4)
    - Duke Marine Laboratory, 1950
      1 film reel: b&w; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: Aerial view of chapel; People walking in quad; Marine Laboratory bldg; Lab Dorms; Lab Workhouse; Inside of lab/people working; Beaufort in distance and old boats that were used; People back in lab; Numbered: 31
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0097)
    - Unknown, Exp. Date: Mar. 1950, 16mm, color, silent; 0:03:50
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0138)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0067, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0138.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0067, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0138.mp4)
    - J. C. Parade at Gardens, undated, 1951; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:08
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: A parade of Duke students (maybe Joe College); Gardens/people sitting; Numbered: 7
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0077)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0048, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0077.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0048, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0077.mp4)
    - Grad Dance. Band & Jean [Levo?], 1951; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:14
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0139)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0068, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0139.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0068, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0139.mp4)
    - Joe College Parade, 1951; 16mm, color, silent; 0:04:50
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0140)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0069, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0140.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0069, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0140.mp4)
    - Card Tricks: Several years, '51, '52, and others, 1951-1952
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0064)
    - Marine Laboratory Kodachrome Original, circa 1951; 16mm, black-and-white and color, silent; 0:17:17
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 18, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0120)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0061, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0120_0121.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0061, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0120_0121.mp4)
    - Marine Lab Orig Optical Soundtrack Negative, circa 1951; 16mm, sound; 0:21:02
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 18, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0121)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0061, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0120_0121.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0061, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0120_0121.mp4)
    - Duke Band, 1952
      Note on can: This film includes: Band Day (W. & L. Game); Tennessee-Duke (Pre-game to half time); N. C. State at Raleigh; Virginia at Charlottesville; '52 Homecoming; '52 Duke-Georgia Tech (Pre-game and half time crowning of Queen.); '52 Duke-Wake Forest
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 19, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0119)
    - Pics of Coombs, Armed Forces, 1952-05; 16mm, color, silent; 0:03:06
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0141)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0070, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0141.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0070, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0141.mp4)
    - Football: Duke -Tenn. Composite Sound Print, 1953
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0067)
    - Football: Duke -Tenn. Composite Sound Print #2, 1953
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0068)
    - Football: Duke - Tenn. HiLites Magnetic Sound, 1953
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0069)
    - Duke Band in Stadium, 1953; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:34
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Looks like what is now Wallace Wade Stadium; Drum corps on field; Duke Band coming out on field/performs/at the end spells out D-U-K-E; Numbered: 6
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0076)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0047, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0076.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0047, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0076.mp4)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1953
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Football play in process; Beautiful run for gain; (38) Duke quarterback/other numbers 86, 28, 74 drive down about 15 yard line almost at the goal line; No score; Numbered: 18
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0087)
    - Duke Band, 1953
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; Numbered: 23
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0090)
    - Marine Lab, 1953-01; 16mm, color, silent; 0:04:13
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 1, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0143)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0072, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0143.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0072, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0143.mp4)
    - Aerials (left over) Jumpy, 1953-06; 16mm, color, silent; 0:04:03
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 2, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0144)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0073, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0144.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0073, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0144.mp4)
    - Garden shots, 1953-06; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:11
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 2, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0145)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0074, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0145.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0074, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0145.mp4)
    - Duke-Army Highlights, Comp. Sound, Print I, circa 1953; 16mm, black-and-white, sound; 0:07:04
      1 film reel: sd., b&w; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: Panning down from quad toward athletic field; Teams playing on field; Scoreboard-apparently no score; Narrator-Ad Penfield, Edited by Tommy O'Boyle; Numbered: 32
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0098)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0053, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0098.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0053, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0098.mp4)
    - Duke-Army Titles - Campus Views, circa 1953; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:01:10
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0108)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0058, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0108.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0058, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0108.mp4)
    - Old Athletics, circa 1953; 16mm, black-and-white, sound;
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7 inch can.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0115)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0060, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0115.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0060, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0115.mp4)
    - Army-Duke Band, 1954
      1 film reel: b&w; 3 inch.; From Description of Films: Band on field, another band getting ready to go out on field; Duke going through formations; Numbered: 17
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0086)
    - This is Duke, 1954
      Produced for Alumni Affairs, this promotional film is presented as a tour of the campus by a student. It contains footage of campus life, religious activities, commencement, homecoming, Joe College Weekend, classrooms, laboratories, the hospital, professional schools, and Duke Forest. A section towards the end has footage of many senior administrators. From a note in the University Archives collection file: The film This is Duke University was a 27-minute film done in the 1950s. Fred Whitener photographed most of the film and produced it. Harry Owen did the sound recording and titles. A mechanical engineering student (an announcer for WDBS, who had a good deep voice) did the narration. The film had a musical background. Allan Bone selected the music from records and it was dubbed with narration. Engineering did the sound recording on the equipment in the photograph. The film was shown all over the world, including on cruise ships. The total costs of this first film with sound, including a trip to N.Y. by Fred Whitenener and Harry Owen, was less than $1,000. Dr. Owen said it should be copied to video tape. Harry Owen, 6/12/85.; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-1; Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-1
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0128)
    - This is Duke, 1954
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0129)
    - This is Duke University, Track - Pos, 1954
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0130)
    - Football Crowd Scenes, 1954; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:03:33
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 2, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0151)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0077, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0151.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0077, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0151.mp4)
    - Under-Exposed. Use as leader, 1954-04
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0146)
    - Football, 1954-07
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0147)
    - Band, D. Perdue, Pre-Game, 1954-10
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0148)
    - Marching Band, Oyster Bowl, Norfolk, Va., 1954-11; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:03:48
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 2, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0149)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0075, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0149.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0075, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0149.mp4)
    - Athletics at Duke University, 1954-12; 16mm, color, sound; 0:02:33
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 2, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0150)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0076, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0150.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0076, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0150.mp4)
    - Orange Bowl Parade, 1955; 16mm, color, silent; 0:05:38
      1 film reel: col.; 5 inch.; From Description of Films: (very dark probably unusable); 350-400 ft; Numbered: 41
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0102)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0008, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0102.mov)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0008, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0102.mp4)
    - Campus Scenes, 1955; 16mm, color, silent; 0:05:55
      1 film, no reel, no core, in 7 inch can.; Note on can: 1. Girls in bedroom; 2. Boy in arch; 3. Doctor & Nurse; 4. Old Classroom Shots; 5. Shots of Chapel; 6. The End Electron Microscope; 7. Campus Shots; Numbered: C-146